(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-21T17:39:44.268318",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
兎田ぺこら BIRTHDAY LIVE 新衣装お披露目
Usada Pekora Birthday Live: New Outfit Reveal
3RD GENERATION USADA PEKORA BIRTHDAY LIVE 2023
3rd Generation - Usada Pekora Birthday Live 2023
オーベイベベイ 今日も明日も
Oh baby, baby, today and tomorrow too,
踏み出してラストシンデレラ
Step forward as the last Cinderella,
不器用な愛を掲げながら
Holding up an awkward love,
ずっと駆け抜けてく強く強く
Running through it, stronger and stronger,
スターラブレイション
Star Lovevation!
「素直になっていいんだよ?」
"Can you just be honest with yourself?"
君はそう言って微笑むの
you say with a gentle smile.
真夜中のラブストーリー 泣きそうに
A midnight love story, looking like you're about to cry,
涙をこらえているんだ
holding back your tears.
分かっているんだよ
I know you understand it, too.
大丈夫が口癖なのは
Your favorite phrase is always "I'm fine".
この先はラブストーリー? それともソリー?
Is it a love story from here? Or is it sorry?
甘いようでスパイシー
It's sweet yet spicy.
ドラマチックな恋も チュールドレス姿も
Dramatic love and even the tulle dress,
脱ぎ捨ててここまで 全速力で
I've left them behind and rushed here at full speed!
(来たんだよ)
(You made it!)
オーベイベベイ 今日も明日も
Oh baby, baby, today and tomorrow too,
踏み出してラストシンデレラ
Step forward as the last Cinderella,
泣き笑いしながら見る空は
The sky I look up at while crying and smiling
最高に美しいんだ
is the most beautiful thing ever.
オーベイベベイ 胸の中の
Oh baby, baby, the feelings in my heart
想いよ高く舞い上がれ
Let them soar high up into the sky,
不器用な愛を掲げながら
Holding up an awkward love,
ずっと駆け抜けてく強く強く
Running through it, stronger and stronger,
スターラブレイション
Star Lovevation!
誤解される性格だから
Because of my misunderstood personality,
また心が疲れるんだね
my heart gets exhausted again.
この先もそうやって強がり言って
Will I keep acting tough like this from now on,
同じように生きてくの?
and live the exact same way?
星巡るこの夜に 何かが揺れ始めた
On this starry night, something began to stir,
描いた理想の自分になるため
To become the ideal self I've always imagined
(走り出す)
(I start running)
オーベイベベイ 今日も明日も
Oh baby, baby, today and tomorrow too,
踏み出してラストシンデレラ
Step forward as the last Cinderella,
鏡の前に立つ私は
The me standing in front of the mirror
最高に美しいんだ
is the most beautiful thing ever.
オーベイベベイ 胸の中の
Oh baby, baby, the feelings in my heart
迷う心よ舞い散らせて
Let my wavering heart scatter away,
弱さ越えてくこの笑顔は
This smile overcoming all my weakness
光る風の中の太陽なんだ
is the sun shining within the radiant wind.
スターラブレイション
Star Lovevation!
雲一つ無い空に
In a sky without a single cloud,
両手一杯の愛が
A love filling both my hands
真っ直ぐに君へと届けに行くよ
is going straight to reach you.
(どこまでも)
(No matter where you are)
オーベイベベイ 今日も明日も
Oh baby, baby, today and tomorrow too,
踏み出してラストシンデレラ
Step forward as the last Cinderella,
泣き笑いしながら見る空は
The sky I look up at while crying and smiling
最高に美しいんだ
is the most beautiful thing ever.
オーベイベベイ 胸の中の
Oh baby, baby, the feelings in my heart
想いよ高く舞い上がれ
Let them soar high up into the sky,
不器用な愛を掲げながら
Holding up an awkward love,
ずっと駆け抜けてく強く強く
Running through it, stronger and stronger,
スターラブレイション
Star Lovevation!
私が私の事を愛して 何が悪いのか? 嫉妬でしょうか?
Lovin' myself, what's wrong with that? Is it jealousy?
私が私の事を愛して
Lovin' myself,
何が悪いのか? 嫉妬でしょうか?
what's wrong with that? Is it jealousy?
痛いとか変わってるとか 届きませんね
"So weird" or "You've changed", I don't care
そのリプライ
about those replies.
大好きな お洋服
In my favorite clothes,
大好きな お化粧で
and my favorite makeup,
お決まりの ハーフツイン巻いて お出かけしよう
With my signature half-twintails, let's go out!
日傘持って ぼっちだって 幸せだもん!
With a parasol, even all alone, I'm so happy!
Chu! 可愛くてごめん 生まれきちゃってごめん
Chu! Sorry for being cute, sorry for being born!
Chu! あざとくてごめん 気になっちゃうよね?ごめん
Chu! Sorry for being a tease, sorry for catching your eye!
Chu! 可愛くてごめん 努力しちゃっててごめん
Chu! Sorry for being cute, sorry for working hard!
Chu! 尊くてごめん 女子力高くてごめん ムカついちゃうよね? ざまぁw
Chu! Sorry for being precious, sorry for my high girly power, does it piss you off? Too bad!
貴方は貴方の事だけどうぞ 私に干渉しないでください
Mind your own business, please don't interfere with me.
類は友を呼ぶと言うけれど...届きませんね その陰口
They say birds of a feather flock together... But your gossip doesn't reach me.
重い厚底ブーツ お気に入りのリュックで
In heavy platform boots and my favorite backpack,
崩せない前髪 くしでといて お出かけしよう
With my unshakeable bangs combed out, let's go out!
軽い女?ふざけんな 重すぎっつーの!
"Easy girl"? Don't mess with me, I'm way too heavy!
Chu! 可愛くてごめん この時代生きてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being cute, sorry for living in this era!
Chu! 目立っててごめん 意識しちゃうよね?ごめん
Chu! Sorry for standing out, sorry for making you notice me!
Chu! 可愛くてごめん 自分磨きしてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being cute, sorry for polishing myself up!
Chu! ぶりっこでごめん 虜にしちゃってごめん ムカついちゃうでしょ? ざまぁw
Chu! Sorry for acting cutesy, sorry for making you fall for me, does it piss you off? Too bad!
自分の味方は自分でありたい 一番大切にしてあげたい
I want to be my own ally, I want to cherish myself above all.
理不尽な我慢はさせたくない それが私
I won't let myself endure unreasonable things, that's who I am.
Chu! 可愛くてごめん 生まれきちゃってごめん
Chu! Sorry for being cute, sorry for being born!
Chu! あざとくてごめん 人生楽しんでごめん
Chu! Sorry for being a tease, sorry for enjoying life!
Chu! 可愛くてごめん 努力しちゃっててごめん
Chu! Sorry for being cute, sorry for working hard!
Chu! 尊くてごめん 女子力高くてごめん ムカついちゃうよね? ざまぁw
Chu! Sorry for being precious, sorry for my high girly power, does it piss you off? Too bad!
はーいみんな！一曲目はスターラプレッション、そして二曲目は可愛くてごめんぺこでした！
Hi everyone! The first song was Star Love Portion, and the second was Kawaikute Gomen, peko!
どうぺこか？どうぺこか？
How was it? How was it?
このあとはみんなお待ちかねのコラボパート行くぺこ！久しぶりの人や初めて会った人、おなじみの人もいるぺこだし！後半にはついにあれが…ってのを見せてくるぺこ！準備してくる！
After this is the long-awaited collab part, peko! There are people we haven't seen in a while, people meeting for the first time, and familiar faces too! And in the second half, finally, that thing... I'll show it to you! I'll go get ready!
じゃねー！
See ya!
任務もメモも やーもやなキミも おあゆね準備はいーい?
Mission memos, you who are hesitant too, are you ready?
スキ！サン！サン！ペーイ！いちにーさんはい！ ポジティブ☆ダンスタイム
Ski! San! San! Pei! One, two, three, yes! Positive Dance Time!
夢色を奏でる夜空で
In the dream-colored night sky,
さぁ shall we dance?
shall we dance?
明日に笑われるくらい
So much that tomorrow might laugh,
しかめ面お月様も一緒に
even the frowning moon joins in,
shall we dance?
最高の気分ね
what a wonderful feeling!
1・2・3のリズムで
With a 1, 2, 3 rhythm,
1・2・3魔法をかけて
cast a 1, 2, 3 magic spell!
キミだけのステップだから
Because it's your own special step,
世界がほら輝くの
look how the world starts to shine!
wake up! wake up!
遅れないでよね魅惑のダンスタイム
Don't be late for this alluring dance time!
jumping! jumping!
恥ずかしがらずに
Without any shyness,
fly! high! fly! high!
high! high! high! high!
dancing☆dancing☆time
Dancing☆ dancing☆ time,
dancing☆ dancing☆ time!
パピプペポジティブ☆ダンスタイム
Papi-pu-pe-positive☆ dance time!
嫌なことも let's dance! let's dance! let's dance!
Leave all your worries behind and let's dance!
キミと一緒に踊れば
If I dance along with you,
dancing☆dancing☆time
dancing☆ dancing☆ time,
dancing☆ dancing☆ time!
今は冴えないメロディでも
Even with an uninspired melody,
夢色に let's be ambitious!
let's be ambitious in dream colors!
きっと届くから
It will surely reach you!
雲色を奏でる夜空で shall we dance?
In the cloud-colored night sky, shall we dance?
昨夜を笑い飛ばすくらい
So much that you laugh away last night,
泣き虫なお星様も一緒に shall we dance?
even the crybaby stars join in, shall we dance?
笑顔にしちゃおう
Let's turn it into smiles!
1・2・3のリズムで
With a 1, 2, 3 rhythm,
1・2・3魔法をかけて
cast a 1, 2, 3 magic spell!
キミだけのステップだから
Because it's your own special step,
世界がほら輝いた！
look how the world started to shine!
wake up! wake up!
止まらないでよね素敵なダンスタイム
Don't stop this wonderful dance time!
jumping! jumping!
無我夢中でほら
lost in the moment, look!
fly! high! fly! high! いえーい！
fly! high! fly! high! Yeah!
dancing☆dancing☆time
Dancing☆ dancing☆ time,
dancing☆ dancing☆ time!
パピプペポジティブ☆ダンスタイム
Papi-pu-pe-positive☆ dance time!
前を向いて let's dance! let's dance! let's dance!
Face forward and let's dance!
キミと一緒に奏でよう
Let's perform together with you,
dancing☆dancing☆time
dancing☆ dancing☆ time,
dancing☆ dancing☆ time!
今は慣れないメロディでも
Even with an unfamiliar melody now,
夢色に let's be ambitious!
let's be ambitious in dream colors!
きっと届くから
It will surely reach you!
準備はいい？
Are you ready?
wake up! wake up!
遅れないでよね超最高のダンスタイム
Don't be late for the ultimate dance time!
jumping! jumping!
思いのままほら
just as you feel, look!
fly! high! fly! high! high! high! high! high!
だから素晴らしいの
That's why it's wonderful!
dancing☆dancing☆time
Dancing☆ dancing☆ time,
dancing☆ dancing☆ time!
パピプペポジティブ☆ダンスタイム
Papi-pu-pe-positive☆ dance time!
涙拭いて let's dance! let's dance! let's dance!
Wipe your tears and let's dance!
キミと一緒に踊れば
If I dance along with you,
dancing☆dancing☆time
dancing☆ dancing☆ time,
dancing☆ dancing☆ time!
今は真っ白なキャンバスも
Even a pure white canvas right now,
君色に let's be ambitious!
let's be ambitious in your color!
描けるのもう一回！？
Can we paint it once more!?
ポジティブ☆ダンスタイム
Positive☆ dance time!
dancing☆dancing☆time
Dancing☆ dancing☆ time,
dancing☆ dancing☆ time!
パピプペポジティブ☆ダンスタイム
Papi-pu-pe-positive☆ dance time!
みんなでさぁ！let's dance! let's dance! let's dance!
Everyone, come on, let's dance!
楽しい！楽しい！優勝だね！
It's so fun! We win!
虹色の毎日をずっとずっと
Rainbow-colored days, always and forever,
笑い疲れるくらい踊っていたい
I want to dance until I'm tired of laughing,
let's be ambitious!
でも今日は おやすみ
But today, good night!
まみむめモヤモヤなキミも
Are you ready, you hazy folks
are you ready? 準備は良い？
getting ready? Are you ready?
スキップ＆クラップで
With a skip and a clap,
いち・にー・さんは いー！
one, two, three, go!
ポジティブ☆ダンスタイム
Positive☆ dance time!
夢色を奏でる夜空で
In the dream-colored night sky,
さぁ shall we dance?
shall we dance?
明日に笑われるくらい
So much that tomorrow might laugh,
しかめ面お月様も一緒に
even the frowning moon joins in,
shall we dance?
最高の気分ね
what a wonderful feeling!
1・2・3のリズムで
With a 1, 2, 3 rhythm,
1・2・3魔法をかけて
cast a 1, 2, 3 magic spell!
キミだけのステップだから
Because it's your own special step,
世界がほら輝くの
look how the world starts to shine!
wake up! wake up!
遅れないでよね魅惑のダンスタイム
Don't be late for this alluring dance time!
jumping! jumping!
恥ずかしがらずに
Without any shyness,
fly! high! fly! high!
high! high! high! high!
毎日ほら
Every single day, look!
ずっとずっと
Always and forever,
笑い疲れるくらい
until we're tired of laughing,
踊っていたい
I want to keep dancing,
let's be ambitious!
でも今日は おやすみ
But today, good night!
まみむめモヤモヤなキミも
Are you ready, you hazy folks
are you ready? 準備はいい？
getting ready? Are you ready?
ポジティブ☆ダンスタイム！
Positive☆ dance time!
あー、恋の定義がわからない
Ah, I don't know the definition of love,
まずスキって基準もわからない
I don't even know what qualifies as liking someone.
要は、恋してるときが恋らしい
In short, being in love feels like love.
客観？主観？エビデンスプリーズ！
Objective? Subjective? Evidence, please!
愛は計算じゃ解けない
Love can't be solved with calculations,
まず普通の計算も解けない
in fact, I can't even solve normal math.
要は、そんな状態が愛らしい
In short, that exact state is adorable.
もう大抵の事象においてQがあってAを出して解けるのに
Most things have a Q and an A to solve them,
勘違いで間違って解のないこの気持ちはなんだろう
so what is this feeling with no right answer?
DANCING!! モーションは相対性にステイ
DANCING!! Motion stays relative,
チューリングラブ 見つめあったって解けないメロウ
Turing Love: even staring doesn't unravel this mellow feeling.
ワットイズラブ いま123で証そうか
What Is Love? Shall we prove it now with 1, 2, 3?
言葉で生み出すクエストョン
A question born from words!
ハートで鳴り響くアンサー
An answer echoing in our hearts!
測ってたって不確実性 ぼくらのBPM
Measured yet uncertain, our BPM!
チューリングラブ 宙に舞ったって信じられないけど
Turing Love: even floating in the sky is hard to believe,
フォーリングラブ いまはABCすらバグりそうだ
Falling Love: right now even ABCs seem to bug out.
なんだか教えてオイラー
Tell me why, Euler!
感想きかせてフェルマー
Let me hear your thoughts, Fermat!
予測不可能性 いま触れてみる
Unpredictability—let's touch it right now!
さぁ証明しよう 間違いのないように
Come on, let's prove it without any mistakes,
証明しよう この感情全部全部
let's prove all of these emotions,
証明しよう 正解があるなら
let's prove it if there's a correct answer,
証明しよう シンプルなQ.E.D.
let's prove a simple Q.E.D.!
今日こそ証明したい！
Today I definitely want to prove it!
目に見えない 無理難題を ASAP!
Unseen impossible riddles, ASAP!
あー、恋の定義がわからない
Ah, I don't know the definition of love,
まずスキって基準もわからない
I don't even know what qualifies as liking someone.
要は、恋してるときが恋らしい
In short, being in love feels like love.
客観？主観？エビデンスプリーズ！
Objective? Subjective? Evidence, please!
あー、恋の定義がわからない
Ah, I don't know the definition of love
まずスキって基準もわからない
First of all, I don't even know what "like" is
要は、恋してるときが恋らしい
In short, being in love is what feels like love
客観? 主観? エビデンスプリーズ!
Objective? Subjective? Evidence, please!
愛は計算じゃ解けない
Love cannot be solved by calculations
まず普通の計算も解けない
First of all, normal calculations can't be solved either
要は、そんな状態が愛らしい
In short, that kind of state is lovely
もう大半の事象においてQがあってAを出して解けるのに勘違いで間違えて解けないこの気持ちはなんだろう
Even though most phenomena can be solved by having a Q and an output A... What is this feeling of a misunderstanding, a mistake, with no solution?
DAZING!! モーションは相対性にステイ
DAZING!! Motion stays relative
チューリングラブ 見つめあったって解けないメロウ
Turing Love: Even when gazing at each other, it's an unresolved mellow
ワットイズラブ いま 123 で証そうか
What is love? Now let's prove it with 1-2-3
言葉で生み出すクエスチョン
A question born from words
(クエスチョン!)
(Question!)
ハートで鳴り響くアンサー
An answer echoing from the heart
(アンサー!)
(Answer!)
測ったって不確実性 ぼくらの BPM
Measured uncertainty, our BPM
不可思議なこのアノマリーを解き明かす過程さえ必要条件です
Unraveling this mysterious anomaly is a necessary condition
三次元コールで遅れに点
Delayed points in a 3D call
エビカニの距離を求めよ
Find the distance between shrimp and crab
的な感じだと思ってたのに
Even though I thought it was that kind of feeling
フォーリングラブ いまは ABC すらバグりそうだな
Falling in love: Right now, even ABC seems bugged
常識的自由にも乗ってないから 君と生み出して見せたいじゃん
It's not even within common sense freedom, so I want to create and show it with you
三次元感覚世界で置けるこの気持ちの求め方
How to find this feeling placed in a 3D sensory world
ワールドだって
Even if the world is bad,
バットだって
splitting,
割れてってゴールで
and at the goal,
遠くなって揺れるこの気持ちの針も
the needle of this feeling growing distant and swaying also
証明しよう
Let's prove it
(証明しよう)
(Prove it)
間違いのないように
so there's no mistake
(証明しよう)
(Prove it)
この感情全部全部
all of this emotion
(証明しよう)
(Prove it)
正解があるなら
if there is a correct answer
(証明しよう)
(Prove it)
シンプルな Q.E.D.
a simple Q.E.D.
今日こそ証明したい! (しよう!)
Today I want to prove it! (Let's do it!)
目に見えない 無理難題を
Invisible difficult problems
ASAP!
今すぐ証明しよう
Let's prove it right now
ツーリングラブ
Turing Love
見つめあったって消えないメロウ
Even when gazing at each other, an indelible mellow
ワットイズラブ
What is love?
いま私達で証そうか
Now let's prove it among ourselves
言葉で生み出すクエスチョン (クエスチョン!)
A question born from words (Question!)
ハートで鳴り響くアンサー (アンサー!)
An answer echoing from the heart (Answer!)
測ったって不確定性 ぼくらのBPM
Measured uncertainty, our BPM
ツーリングラブ 宙に舞ったってその笑顔も
Turing Love: Even dancing through the skies, that smile too
ファーリングラブ 今はXYZまで分かりそう
Falling Love: Now even XYZ seems understandable
だから仕込まされたピタゴラス
So the rigged Pythagoras
確かに成立してるリマインド
Reminds us that it surely holds true
予測済み完全今触れてみる
Already predicted, perfection, let's touch it right now
さあ証明しよう (証明しよう)
Now let's prove it (Prove it)
間違いのないように (証明しよう)
so there's no mistake (Prove it)
この感情全部全部 (証明しよう)
all of this emotion (Prove it)
世界があるなら (証明しよう)
if there is a world (Prove it)
シンプルなQ.E.D. (証明しよう)
a simple Q.E.D. (Prove it)
世界があるなら (証明しよう)
if there is a world (Prove it)
すれ違いを超えて (証明しよう)
transcending misunderstandings (Prove it)
間違いのないように (証明しよう)
so there's no mistake (Prove it)
この感情全部全部 (証明しよう)
all of this emotion (Prove it)
世界があるなら (証明しよう)
if there is a world (Prove it)
シンプルなQ.E.D. (証明しよう)
a simple Q.E.D. (Prove it)
世界があるなら (証明しよう)
if there is a world (Prove it)
すれ違いを超えて (証明しよう)
transcending misunderstandings (Prove it)
間違いのないように (証明しよう)
so there's no mistake (Prove it)
シンプルなQ.E.D.
a simple Q.E.D.
この気持ちー止まりませーん!!!!
This feeling... won't stop—!!!!
君と育った馴染みで生まれたい
I want to be born in the familiarity grown with you
東に西に住んでてほしい
I want you to live in the east and the west
そして大人になって突然再会してみたいってね！
And then suddenly reunite after becoming adults, you know!
もしくは第一印象最悪な初対面だったり
Or maybe having a first impression that was a terrible first meeting
ごちゃまぜ大シチュエーション
A mixed-up grand situation
実況君が隠す組織と戦うヒーローだって言う秘密があったり
Having a secret like being a hero fighting an organization hidden by a commentator
七転八倒 独り占めしたいな
Tumbling around, I want to keep you all to myself
ああ 君に出会った日から私の毎日がラブコメディに変わったんだ
Ah, from the day I met you, my every day turned into a romantic comedy
君が君であるためのサンライズすべてが弾けそうなんだ
Everything that makes you who you are seems like it's going to burst like a sunrise
もうだめだ お手上げれない いつかは結ばれますように
No good anymore, I give up, hoping we'll be tied together someday
そんな恋に予期なしに訪れるんだ
Such love visits unexpectedly
髪をほどいたわたし見て 君がキュンとキュンとしますように
Seeing me with my hair undone, I hope you go "kyun, kyun!"
君がキュンとキュンとしますように
I hope you go "kyun, kyun!"
ひとめ見たときピピッときて
The moment I laid eyes on you, ping!
すっかり電気が走った
Electricity suddenly pulsed through me!
絶対絶対絶対これは運命だ
Definitely, definitely, definitely, this is destiny!
ねえ ほら ドキドキしてやばいのだ
Hey, look, my heart is racing like crazy!
世界中で君だけだよ 叫んじゃいたいぜ
You're the only one in the world, I want to shout it out!
すきすきすきすきすきすき
Love! Love! Love! Love! Love! Love!
君を振り向かせるにはどうしたらいいんだろう
How can I make you turn around and look at me?
私は私のまま君に伝えればいいんだよね
I should just tell you how I feel, just as I am.
ああ 誰でも主人公なんだ 他の誰でもない私を生きてゆくんだ
Ah, everyone is the protagonist of their own life.
すきすきすきすきすきすきすきすき
Love, love, love, love...
君が君であるための存在すべてが
Everything about your existence just as you are
弾けそうなんだ もうだめだ おさえきれない
Is about to burst, I can't hold it back anymore!
いつか結ばれますように
Hoping we'll be together one day!
すき！すき！すき！すき！
Love! Love! Love! Love!
君がくれたたくさんの気持ちのすべてが
All the countless feelings you gave me
こぼれそうなんだ もうだめだ この思いが
Are about to spill over, I can't take it anymore!
ぎゅぎゅっと伝わりますように
I hope they reach you with a tight squeeze!
すき！すき！すき！すき！すき！すき！
Love! Love! Love! Love! Love! Love!
全速力の向こうに 何かがきっときっと待ってる
Beyond running at full speed, something is waiting for me
曲がり角で君に会えますように
Hoping I can meet you at the corner!
すきすきすきすきすきすき
Love, love, love, love...
何もかもが... すきです
Everything... I love it!
サラバ、愛しき悲しみたちよ
Farewell, my beloved sorrows!
行くの？行かないの？どっちゅーいんじゃ
Going? Not going? Which is it?
言えよ 言いたいよ バッサリ言えない
Say it, I want to say it, but I can't say it clearly!
裏か表か底無しのクエスチョン だけどどうしてどうにもこうにもたいたい
Front or back, a bottomless question, but why can't I do anything?
見上げる 言わざる 聞かざるでござる君子
Looking up, speaking no evil, hearing no evil, like a gentleman
危うきに近寄らずデス
Stay away from danger, they say!
お願いされたらやめたくなります だったら許すたてるわらえ
If you ask me, I'd want to stop, but if so, smile!
こころの声音が木霊する 涙と希望のカーニバル
The voice of my heart echoes, a carnival of tears and hope
生意気くらいの夜明けに
In a sassy, impudent dawn!
サラバ、昨日をぬぎすてて 勇気の声をふりしぼれ
Farewell, cast off yesterday and muster the voice of courage!
「じぶん」という名の愛を知るために
To know the love named "myself"!
眠れない羊の群れよ 迷えるこころの叫びをくりかえす
Oh flock of sleepless sheep, repeating the screams of a wandering heart
我らの世界はまだ始まったばかりさ
Our world has only just begun!
行くの？ 行かないの？ 行っちまえばいーじゃん
Going? Not going? Might as well just go!
言えよ 言いたいよ
Speak up, I want to say it...
寂しい思い出ひとつ天幕を
A single lonely memory, inside the tent...
やるの？
Doing it?
サボるの？ サボればいーじゃん
Slacking off? Might as well slack off!
遭難しそうでまさかの号泣
Looking like a shipwreck, weeping unexpectedly.
褒めてますから全力で
I'm praising you with all my might.
そしてどこまでも
And no matter how far...
続く夢を見た
I saw a continuing dream.
天使が舞い降りてきた
An angel came dancing down.
そしてどこまでも 続く空のもとで
And under the endless sky stretching on forever,
自由になりたい
I want to be free.
1, 2 and 3, 4, 5 Get up, stand up, free your soul
1, 2 and 3, 4, 5 Stand up and make some noise!
Oh-ho do it, do it, Oh-ho do it, do it
Oh-ho do it, do it, Oh-ho do it now,
心の声が木霊する
The voice of my heart echoes out.
涙と希望のカーニバル
A carnival of tears and hope.
生意気くらいの夜明けに
In a dawn as sassy as this.
揺らすんだ…
Shake it up...
進むんだ…
Move forward...
サラバ、昨日をぬぎすてて 勇気の声をとれ
Farewell, shed yesterday and take up the voice of courage.
「じぶん」という名の愛を知るために
To know the love called 'myself'.
眠れない羊の群れよ
O flock of sleepless sheep,
迷える心の叫びを 振り返るな 我らの世界はまだ始まったばかりだ
Don't look back at the cries of a straying heart, our world has only just begun.
始まったばかりだ
Only just begun.
Ah-Ha Dig it, Dig it, Ah-Ha Dig it, Dig it
Oh-ho do it, do it, Oh-ho do it, do it
Oh-ho do it now, do it now, do it now
あわれみをお下りなさい
Show me some pity...
落ちた小鳥にそっと触れるような悲しみをください
Give me a sorrow like gently touching a fallen little bird.
涙ぐんで見下ろして かわいそうだと口に出して
Look down with tearful eyes and call it pitiful.
靴の先で転がしても構わないわ 汚れていてもいいからと
You can kick me with the tip of your shoe, even if I'm filthy.
泥だらけの手を取って ねぇ輪になって踊りましょう
Take my mud-covered hand, hey, let's form a circle and dance.
目障りな有象無象は全て食べてしまいましょう
Let's devour all the annoying riffraff.
スパイスは堪え難いくらいがいいわ
The spice should be hard to bear.
lie, lie, lie, la la la...
怯えた小鳥は さよならなんて言えなくて
The frightened little bird couldn't even say goodbye.
愛を乞う仕草で黙り込んで つつましいつもりでいた
Remaining silent with gestures begging for love, thinking it was modest.
lie, lie, it’s a lie, not a lie, もう辛い
lie, lie, it’s a lie, not a lie, it's already too painful.
散々傷ついて やさしいせかいに誰だって行きたいわ
Hurt over and over, anyone would want to go to a gentle world.
ひとつに溶けてしまいましょう 憎しみも愛情もむしゃむしゃと
Let's melt together into one, greedily devouring both hatred and affection.
頬張ってしまいましょう 混沌の甘い甘い壺の中で
Let's stuff our cheeks in the sweet, sweet pot of chaos.
lie, lie, lie, la la la...
曖昧に笑うから 会いたいと思うのよ
You smile so ambiguously, which is why I want to see you.
I know you’re here to stay with me 愛されていたいだけ
I know you’re here to stay with me, I just want to be loved.
lie, lie, lie, you’re to be with me
雷鳴の咲くところ 惨憺たる heavenly feeling
Where thunder blooms, a dismal heavenly feeling.
あわれみを下さい
Have mercy on me,
愁いも愛情も
and sorrow and affection too,
むしゃむしゃと頬張ってしまいましょう
gobbling them all up.
混沌の
In the chaos...
甘い甘い壺の中で
In a jar of sweet, sweet chaos...
ライラライララララ…
Lie, lie, lie, la la la...
逢いには折れそうだから
Because I'm about to break when we meet,
逢いたいと思うのよ
I find myself wanting to see you.
I know you're here to stay with me
愛されていたいだけ
I just want to be loved.
lie, lie, lie, you're to be with me
雷鳴の咲くところ
Where thunder blooms,
惨憺たる heavenly feeling
a wretched, heavenly feeling.
愛だけ残ればいい
It's fine if only love remains.
しんしんと悲しみ
Quietly, only sorrow
だけが降り積もる
rains down and accumulates.
願望も悔恨もただ埋め尽くす
Burying all desires and regrets alike,
絆結んだ遠い春の日を
the distant spring day we bonded--
傷跡さえも消えてしまうの
even the scars vanish away.
やがてキラキラ夢の中 朽ちていく
Soon, within a glittering dream, it decays.
光は貴方に届くはずだから
For the light is bound to reach you,
まぶしくて涙が止まらない
so dazzling that my tears won't stop.
ねえどうか側にいて 泥だらけの手を取って
Please stay by my side, take my mud-stained hand
離さないで どうかずっと側にいて 離さないで
and don't let go. Stay by my side forever.
暗くなるの、側にいて 離さないで、見えないわ
It's getting dark, stay by my side, don't let go, I can't see.
ただずっと側にいて 離さないで、ただずっと愛してるよ
Just stay by my side forever, don't let go, I love you.
世界で一番おひめさま
I'm the number one princess in the world!
そういう扱い心得てよね
Make sure you know how to treat me right!
その一 いつもと違う髪型に気付くこと
1. Notice when my hairstyle is different.
その二 ちゃんといちご靴まで視ること いいね?
2. Look all the way to my strawberry shoes, okay?
その三 わたしの一言には三つの言葉で返事すること
3. Reply to every word I say with three words.
わかったら右手がお留守なのをなんとかして!
Once you understand, do something about my empty hand!
別にわがままなんて言ってないんだから
It's not like I'm being selfish or anything,
キミに心から思って欲しいの かわいいって
so I want you to truly think from your heart that I'm cute.
世界で一番おひめさま 気付いて ねぇねぇ
Notice I'm the number one princess, hey, hey!
待たせるなんて論外よ わたしを誰だと思ってるの?
Making me wait is out of the question. Who do you think I am?
もうなんだか 甘いものが食べたい! 欠点?かわいいの間違いでしょ 文句は許しませんの
Already, I want something sweet! Flaws? You mean cute, right?
あのね?私の話ちゃんと聞いてる?ちょっとぉ…
Hey? Are you actually listening to me? Hello...
あ、それとね?白いおおかみさん 決まっているでしょ?
Oh, and another thing? A white horse, it's decided, right?
迎えに来て わかったらかしずいて 手を取って“おひめさま”って
Come pick me up, take my hand and call me "princess"!
別にわがままなんて言ってないんだから
It's not like I'm being selfish or anything,
でもね 少しくらい怒ってくれたっていいのよ?
but you know, it's fine if you get a little mad at me, right?
世界でわたしだけのおうじさま 気付いて ほらほら おててが空いています
Notice my hand is empty, my only prince in the world.
無口で無愛想なおうじさま もう どうして!
A silent and unsociable prince, why oh why?!
気付いてよ早く みんな みんな 我慢します…
Notice me quickly, everyone is holding back...
わがままな子だと思わないで
Don't think of me as a selfish girl,
後で後悔するわよ 当然でしょ?
you'll regret it later. Of course, right?
だってわたしは 世界で一番おひめさま
Because I am the number one princess in the world!
ちゃんと見ててよね どこかに行っちゃうよ?
Make sure you're watching, or I'll go somewhere else!
ふいに抱きしめられた 急にそんな えッ?
Suddenly embraced, all of a sudden like that, eh?
“躱される 危ないよ” そう言ってそっぽ向くキミ
"You'll dodge it, it's dangerous," you say as you turn away.
世界で一番おひめさま
The number one princess in the world,
そう言う扱い心得てよね
so make sure you know how to treat me!
その一 いつもと違う髪型に気付くこと
Notice when my hair is styled differently!
その二 ちんと靴まで見ること いいね?
Notice down to my shoes, got it?
その三 わたしの一言には三つの言葉で返事すること
Reply to every word with three words!
わかったら右手がお留守なのをなんとかして!
What are you staring at?!
べつにわがままなんて言ってないんだから
I'm not being selfish, you know,
キミに心から思って欲しいの かわいいって
I just want you to think I'm cute!
世界で一番おひめさま
The number one princess in the world!
気がついて ねえねえ
Realize that, hey, hey!
待たせるなんて論外よ
Keeping me waiting is out of the question!
わたしを誰だと思ってるの?
Who do you think I am?!
もうなんだか あまいものが食べたい!
I want something sweet right now!
今すぐに あ、の
Go get it immediately!
欠点? かわいいの間違いでしょ
Flaws? Just cute mistakes!
文句は許しませんの
No complaints allowed!
あのね? わたしの話ちゃんと聞いてる? ちょっと…
Are you even listening to me? Wait...
あ、それとね? 白いおうさま きまってるでしょ?
Oh, and what about a white horse?
迎えにきて
Come and take me away!
わかったらかしずいて 手をとって "おひめさま"って
Take my hand and call me "Princess"!
べつにわがままなんて言ってないんだから
I'm not really being selfish,
でもね 少しくらい叱ってくれたっていいのよ?
though it's okay to scold me a little!
世界でわたしだけのおうさま
My very own prince in the world!
気がついて ほらほら
Realize that, look, look!
おててが空いています
Our hands are empty!
無口でぶあいそうなおうさま
You silent, blunt prince!
もうどうして! 気がついてよはやく
Just notice soon, come on!
絶対キミはわかってない! わかってないわ…
You really don't understand at all!
いちごののったショートケーキ
Shortcake with a strawberry,
こだわりたまごのとろけるプリン
and rich melting pudding.
みんなみんな我慢します…
I hold back on all of them!
わがままな子だと思わないで
Don't think I'm a selfish girl!
わたしだってやればできるもん
I can do it too if I try,
あとで後悔するわよ
and you'll regret it later!
当然です! だってわたしは
Of course, because I am...
そして君が知らずに 幸せな灰になった後で
And after you passed away,
僕は今更 君が好きだって気付いたよ
realizing I loved you all along.
「大人になりたくないよ」なんて大人ぶってさ
"I don't want to grow up,"
駆けた 少年の日
I ran through my youth.
大人になりたくないよなんて大人ぶってさ
"I don't want to grow up,"
駆けた 少年の日
I ran through my youth.
どうやら僕に訪れたいたずらは
The trouble that somehow came my way
相当タチの悪い不死身のおせっかい
was a quite nasty, immortal joke.
神様 素敵なプレゼントをありがとう
"God, thanks for this wonderful present,"
なんて到底マト外れの
was far off the mark.
幼いいたずらの奥に大事に隠した
Deep within the childish prank,
片思いは察してくれないんだよ
my unrequited love goes unnoticed.
追い越してく戻れない憧れ
Chasing it down, I can't turn back.
好きな人にさようならを
Saying goodbye to the one I loved.
いつか見た夕焼けはあんなに綺麗だったのに
The sunset I saw back then was so beautiful,
恋なんて呼ぶには爛れすぎてしまったよ
yet calling it love is too modest.
そして君が知らずに 幸せな灰になった後で
And after you passed away,
僕は今更 君が好きだって気付いたよ
realizing I loved you all along.
百年前の同じ日に君のおばあちゃんは
A hundred years ago on this very day,
同じことを言ったんだ
your grandma said the exact same thing.
君の孫のひまごのその最後に
And at the end, with your great-grandchild,
僕はまたひとりになる
I'll be all alone once again.
うつろっていくメトロポリスと
Metropolis fading into nothingness,
君の名に花束を
dedicating a bouquet to your name.
いつか見た夕焼けはあんなに綺麗だったのに
The sunset I saw back then was so beautiful,
恋なんて呼ぶには遠回しすぎたね
yet calling it love is too far gone.
そして君が知らずに 幸せな灰になった後で
And so, after you unknowingly became happy ashes,
僕は今更 君が好きだったって
I now realize that I loved you all this time.
世界がハイになったとて
Even if the world becomes a heap of ashes,
僕は今でも 風に君を想い出すんだ
I still remember you in the wind even now.
誰もいない 枯れた世界で
In this deserted, withered world,
いたずらの意味を知ったよ
I came to understand the meaning of that prank.
臆病でも 今なら言えるんだ
Even as a coward, I can say it now.
地球最後の告白を
The earth's last confession.
いつか見た夕焼けは あんなにキレイだったのに
The sunset I saw back then was so beautiful, yet
恋なんて呼ぶには 遠回りすぎたよ
calling it love was taking too long of a detour.
そして何もかもが 手遅れの灰になった後で
And after everything became untimely ashes,
僕は今更 君が好きだって
I now realize that I love you...
君が好きだったって言えやしないよ
I can't even say that I loved you.
超天変地異みたいな狂騒にも慣れて
Accustomed to this cataclysmic, otherworldly madness,
こんな日常を平和と見間違う
I mistake this daily life for peace.
ランブリング コースター 揺さぶられながら
As this rambling coaster jolts me back and forth,
見失えないものは何だ?
what is it that I mustn't lose sight of?
平等主義の概念に呑まれて
Drunk on the concept of fundamental equalism,
心までがまるでエトセトラ
feels like even my soul is kind of et cetera.
大嫌い 大好き ちゃんとしゃべらなきゃ
Love it or hate it, you gotta say it clearly,
人形とさして変わらないし
or you're not all that different from a dummy.
宵街を行く人ばかりは
Crowds of people walking the streets at night
嬉しそうだったり寂しそうだったり
some seem to be happy, some seem to be lonely.
コントラストが五線譜を飛び回り
The contrast jumps around the lines of the music score,
歌とリズムになる
creating the song and rhythm.
ママレードにシュガーソング ピーナッツ＆ビターステップ
Marmalade and sugar song, peanuts and bitter step,
甘くて苦くて目が回りそうです
so sweet and then so acrid, it makes my head spin.
南南西を目指してパーティを続けよう
Let's head south-southwest and keep this party going
世界中を驚かせてしまう夜になる
to make it the night that will astonish the world.
I feel 上々 連鎖になってリフレクト
I feel fantastic, reflect that around in a chain.
大前提合理主義の是のにも慣れて
Accustomed to the pros of absolute rationalism,
僕らの音楽は道具になり下がる
our music is reduced to mere tools.
こっちを向いてよ背を向けないでよ
Look this way, don't turn your back on me,
それはセロトニンにならないけど
that won't become serotonin, but...
祭り囃子のその後で
After the festival music fades away,
高ぶったままのひと 泣き出してしまうひと
people still hyped up, people bursting into tears,
多分同じだろう でも言葉にしよものなら
they're probably the same, but if you put it into words,
季節が代わる日に最高だって
on the changing seasons, it's the best.
シュガーソング ジアワーストってリフレクト
Sugar song, the worst? reflect.
死なない理由をそこに映し出せ
Project the reason not to die right there.
欲しがったって高速で明日を巻きちゃうけど
Even if you want tomorrow to speed by,
脳内天的今日のアップデートを果たしたなら
if you've updated your heavenly mindset today,
超天変地異みたいな狂騒にも慣れて
Accustomed to the cataclysmic madness,
こんな日常を平和と見間違う
I mistake my daily life for peace
ランブリング コースター 揺さぶられながら見失わないものは何だ?
As this rambling coaster jolts me, what mustn't I lose sight of?
平等主義概念に飲み込まれて
Drunk on the concept of fundamental equalism,
心までがまるでエトセトラ
Feels like even my soul is kind of et cetera
大嫌い 大好き ちゃんと語らなきゃ
Love it or hate it, you gotta say it clearly
人形と対して変わらないし
Or you're not all that different from a dummy
宵街を往く人かかりは
Ah, crowds of people walking the streets at night,
嬉しそうだったり寂しそうだったり
Some seem to be happy, some seem to be lonely
コントラストが五線譜を飛び回り
The contrast jumps around the lines of the music score
歌とリズムになる
Creating the song and rhythm
ママレードにシュガーソング ピーナッツ&ビターステップ
Marmalade and sugar song, peanuts and bitter step
甘くて苦くて目が回りそうです
So sweet and then so acrid, it makes my head spin
南南西を目指してパーティを続けよう
Let's head south-southwest and keep this party going
世界中を驚かせてしまう夜になる
To make it the night that will astonish the world
I feel 上々 連鎖になってリフレクト
I feel fantastic, reflect that around in a chain
ママレードにシュガーソング ピーナッツ&ビターステップ
Marmalade and sugar song, peanuts and bitter step
甘くて苦くて目が回りそうです
So sweet and then so acrid, it makes my head spin
南南西を目指してパーティを続けよう
Let's head south-southwest and keep this party going
世界中を驚かせてしまう夜になる
To make it the night that will astonish the world
お誕生日おめでとう！
Happy birthday!
新衣装じゃん！可愛いー！
New outfit! So cute!
足元とか見てご覧なさいよ、皆さん！
Look at her feet and stuff, everyone!
人参リボンじゃん！可愛い！お姫様だったんだね！
A carrot ribbon! So cute! Truly a princess!
ぺこらの生誕祭ライブだよ、今日は！
It's Pekora's birthday live today!
人参ペコだよ、これ！
It's Carrot Peko, this!
みんな来てくれてありがとうね、いつもね！
Thanks for everyone coming, as always!
じゃあ、みんな一緒に...よいしょって言おう！せーの、よいしょー！
Then, let's all say "Yoisho" together! Ready, yoisho!
この後も、歌と、お知らせのあれのと、お楽しみに！バイバーイ！
After this, look forward to the song and announcements! Bye-bye!
僕の声は聞こえていますか? Please tell me...
Can you hear my voice? Please tell me...
答えのない虚空目指して fly far away
Aiming for the lofty sky without answers, fly faraway
言葉じゃ足りないから 僕のすべて受け止めて
Because words are not enough, accept my everything
制御出来ない... したくないよ
I can't control it... I don't want to!
初めて知る感覚
This is my first time knowing this sensation
君に 歌うよ 永遠の始まりを
I'll sing to you the origin of eternity
「だから笑って...」
So I'll smile...
誰よりも熱く 誰よりも強く抱き締めるよ
More passionately, more strongly, I'll embrace you
震える 心揺さぶられ ばいい 何かが動き出す
It's okay if my trembling heart shakes, something starts moving
僕等きっと 生まれた日から 出会える日を ずっと探してたんだ
Surely since birth I was searching for the day we'd meet
風の鳴く夜は 思い出して
Remember the night the wind cried
共に奏でた奇蹟 天に舞うよ
The miracle we played together dances in the heavens
僕の想いは届いているかな? true or false
Are my thoughts reaching you? True or false
触れ合うたびもどかしさが募る crying more crying
When we come in contact the frustration mounts, crying more crying
いつも避けてばかりいた明日の見失いそう で
Always avoiding tomorrow, about to lose sight of it
傷付けないように 傷付かないように
So that I won't hurt, so that I won't be hurt
嘘だけが増えていく
Only the lies go on increasing
「だから笑って...」
So I'll smile...
Listen to my song...
僕の声は聞こえていますか?
Can you hear my voice?
Please tell me...
答えのない虚空の空目指し
Aiming for the endless sky without answers,
fly far away
言葉じゃ足りないから 僕のすべて受け止めて
Because words aren't enough, accept my everything.
制御出来ない...したくないよ
I can't control it... I don't want to.
初めて知る感覚
This sensation I'm experiencing for the first time.
君に歌うよ 永遠の始まりを
I'll sing to you of the beginning of eternity
「だから笑って...」
"So please smile..."
誰よりも熱く 誰よりも強く 抱き締めるよ
More passionately than anyone, more strongly than anyone, I'll hold you tight.
震える心 揺さぶればいい 何かが動き出す
It's okay if my trembling heart shakes, something is set in motion.
僕等きっと 生まれた日から 出会える日をずっと探してたんだ
Surely since the day we were born, we've always been searching for the day we could meet.
風の鳴く夜は思い出して 共に奏でた軌跡 天に舞うよ
Remember the night the wind cried, the melody we played together dances to the heavens!
僕の思いは 届いていますか?
Are my feelings reaching you?
true or false 触れ合う度もどかしさが募る
True or false, the frustration grows with every touch.
crying more crying いつも避けてばかりいた
Crying, more crying, I always kept avoiding it,
明日を見失いそうで
As if I were losing sight of tomorrow.
傷付けないように 傷付かないように 嘘だけが増えていく
So as not to hurt, so as not to be hurt, only the lies keep increasing.
「だから笑って...」
"But please smile..."
痛い程に苦しい程に そう...愛おしいから
It hurts so much, it's so agonizing, because... I cherish you so much.
求める気持ち 抑えきれない 自分が怖かった
I couldn't suppress the desire, I was terrified of myself.
やっと身体中巡る本能はrhythmに気付いたんだ
At last, the instinct coursing through my body realized the rhythm.
もう二度と君を離さないよ
I'll never let you go again!
いくつもの昨日がね 未来を照らす
Numerous yesterdays illuminate the future.
この身朽ち果てても 伝えたいものがある
Even if this body decays, there is something I want to convey.
響け命の歌 彼方羽ばたいて 「だから笑って...」
Resonate, song of life, flutter to the distant skies. "So please smile..."
誰よりも熱く 誰よりも強く 抱き締めたい
More passionately than anyone, more strongly than anyone, I want to hold you tight.
震える心 揺さぶればいい 何かが動き出す
It's okay if my trembling heart shakes, something is set in motion.
僕等きっと 生まれた日から 出会える日をずっと探してたんだ
Surely since the day we were born, we've always been searching for the day we could meet.
風の鳴く夜は思い出して 共に紡いだ奇跡 天を描くよ
Remember the night the wind cried, the miracle we spun together portrays the heavens!
この身朽ち果てても 伝えたいものがある
Even if this body decays, there is something I want to convey,
響け命の歌 彼方羽ばたいて 「だから笑って...」
Resonate, song of life, flutter to the distant skies. "So please smile..."
誰よりも熱く 誰よりも強く 抱き締めたい
More passionately than anyone, more strongly than anyone, I want to hold you tight.
震える心 揺さぶればいい 何かが動き出す
It's okay if my trembling heart shakes, something is set in motion.
僕等きっと 生まれた日から 出会える日をずっと探してたんだ
Surely since the day we were born, we've always been searching for the day we could meet.
風の鳴く夜は思い出して 共に紡いだ奇跡
Remember the night the wind cried, the miracle we spun together,
天を描くよ
portrays the heavens!
もう二度と君を離さないよ
I'll never let you go again!
いくつもの昨日がね 未来を照らす
Numerous yesterdays illuminate the future.
この身朽ち果てても 伝えたいものがある
Even if this body decays, there is something I want to convey.
響け命の歌 彼方羽ばたいて
Resonate, song of life, flutter to the distant skies.
「だから笑って...」
"So please smile..."
誰よりも熱く 誰よりも強く 抱き締めたい
More passionately than anyone, more strongly than anyone, I want to hold you tight.
震える心 揺さぶればいい 何かが動き出す
It's okay if my trembling heart shakes, something is set in motion.
僕等きっと 生まれた日から 出会える日をずっと探してたんだ
Surely since the day we were born, we've always been searching for the day we could meet.
風の鳴く夜は思い出して 共に紡いだ奇跡 天を描くよ
Remember the night the wind cried, the miracle we spun together portrays the heavens!
みんな、みんな！
Everyone, everyone!
どうペコだった？可愛かった？
How was Pekora? Was she cute?
そんな君にお知らせだ！それは、こちら！
I have an announcement for you all! It is right here!
うさだぺこら誕生日記念2023のグッズ発売！ということで商品は、こちら！
Usada Pekora's 2023 Birthday Celebration merchandise release! The items are right here!
こちら、ね、はぐれ先生の描き下ろしの等身大タペストリーと今年は、何年ペコですか？そう！うさぎ年ということで
First off, we have the life-sized tapestry illustrated by Hagure-sensei! And what year is it this year? That's right! The Year of the Rabbit,
大願成就の絵馬とお守り！しかもこのお守りは超幸運お守りぺこだから、これを持ってたら確実…いや、個人差ありますぺこですけども、きっと運がいい間違いなし！
so we have the prayer ema and amulet! And since this amulet is a super lucky amulet, if you have this, you're guaranteed... well, individual differences apply, but you're definitely going to have good luck!
そして野うさぎのティッシュカバー！こちらがペコちゃんの誕生日記念グッズとなっております！
And the wild rabbit tissue cover! These are Pekora-chan's birthday celebration goods!
どうペコですか？可愛くないペコですか？タペストリーと絵馬はね、はぐれママの描き下ろしなのでぜひぜひ、そして
How is it? Isn't it cute? The tapestry and ema are illustrated by Hagure Mama, so please definitely check them out!
ペコラの一押しはやっぱ幸運お守りかなって思ってみんながねうさぎ年をね、あの幸せに暮らせるようにこのお守りをね、いつも肌身離さず持っていたらきっといいことが絶対に起きるペコだからぜひお迎えを！
And Pekora's top recommendation is probably the lucky amulet! I hope everyone can live happily in the Year of the Rabbit, so if you keep this amulet close to you always, something wonderful will definitely happen to you, so please grab one!
あとティッシュカバーもね、あの寒い時期とかに鼻かんでヨーロッパコです。そしてこちらね、あのフルセットで買っていただいた方にはうさだぺこら箔押し複製サイン＆メッセージ入りのあの
And the tissue cover too, you can blow your nose during the cold season, very Pekora. And for those who buy the full set, you'll get a postcard with Usada Pekora's foil-stamped duplicate signature and message!
ポストカードが付いてくるので
It comes with a postcard,
ぜひぜひ皆さんよろしくお願いします！
so everyone, please check it out!
そしたら、
And so,
この後ね、分かってる人はいると思うんだけど、
well, after this, I think some of you already know,
メンバー限定でアンコールライブもあるぺこなので、
there will also be a member-only encore live,
ぜひお忘れなくよろしくぺこね！
so please don't forget!
てなわけで、今日もね、みんな本当にいつもありがとう！
That being said, thank you all so much as always today too!
てなわけで、おつぺこでした！
And with that, good peko!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!